Хей, Сет Роугън. Как е, мой?
О, здрасти Джон! Насам!
Добре дошли в
Международно летище Лос Анджелис.
Внимание, до всички пътници.
Не оставяйте багажа си без надзор.
Всеки багаж без надзор
е обект на претърсване...
Много сме щастливи!
Виж това!
- Какво става, мой човек?
- Радвам се да те видя, приятел.
- Как я караш?
- Добре съм, човече.
Да, така е.
Колко време мина?
По някое време през последната...
- година или нещо такова.
- Да.
Измислил съм най-добрия уикенд, измислен някога, човече.
- Казвай.
- Не искам да разваля изненадата.
- Сет Роугън!
- Започваме. Хей.
- Как е, човече?
- Да, добре.
Така, значи, ти винаги играеш
един и същ човек в всеки филм.
Кога ще започнеш да се занимаваш
с истинско актьорство, човек?
Добре, благодаря.
Дай ми нещо.
Покажи ми смеха си.
Покажи ми прочутия смях на Сет Роугън.
Сет Роугън, хора.
Добре, пристигнах. Тук съм.
Казахме си здрасти.
Може ли да ходим да
ядем в "При Карл Дж."?
Би било супер, но съм на...
Не мога да ям такива неща сега.
- Аз съм на...
- Какво?
Аз съм на прочистване.
На какво?
На прочистване съм.
- Какво?
- Добре е за теб.
Не знаех...
Трябвало е да сереш шест пъти дневно.
- Това не е вярно.
- Вярно е!
- Трябва да сереш два пъти дневно.
- Не.
Не е вярно.
Това си го мислеха преди.
Сега знаят, че трябва да
сереш шест пъти дневно.
Значи не пиеш...
Не пушиш трева. Не...
- Не, не правя ги тия неща.
- Но...
Аз съм на прочистване. Не съм психопат.
Виж, човече, ако спреш да ядеш глутен
ще се чувстваш много по-добре цял ден.
Винаги, когато се чувстваш гадно,
това е заради глутена.
- Не е вярно.
- Вярно е!
- Кой ти казва да не го ядеш?
- Просто е вярно.
- Ти дори не знаеш какво означава глутен.
- Знам какво е.
- Не, не знаеш.
- Знам какво значи "глутен".
Глутен е неясен термин.
Използва се, за да поставя
в категории вредните неща, сещаш ли се?
Калориите, мазнините...
Някой просто ти е казал, че
не трябва да го ядеш
и ти си започнал:
"Предполагам, че не трябва."
Глутен означава вредни неща, и
няма да го ям.
Боже!
Всяка хапка е по-добра от предишната.
- Това е то.
- Глутен!
- Хей, това е красиво.
- Да. Кефи ли те? Пренаправено е.
- Супер е.
- Чисто ново е. Тези са нови.
- Боже господи!
- Много е готино, нали?
Значи така живее другата половина.
- Стига.
- Страхотно!
- Маси за въздушен хокей.
- Исусе!
- Нали? Окей, готви се, Джей.
- За какво?
- Имам малка изненада за теб.
- Добре.
Ето ти най-добрия уикенд
в живота ти.
- Погледни само, човече.
- Боже... Сериозно ли?
Всички твои любими неща.
- Дъвки, гумени бонбони върху...
- Да.
И пише "Джей".
- Със джойнтове.
Пише "Джей" със "Дж"-та.
Ти си велик.
Хайде, знам, че не ти харесва в ЛА,
затова реших да направя...
Знаеш, да "смажа" влизането.
- Улеснява прехода.
- Нали?
Това е много необходимата любовна игра.
- Знаеш ли какво още имам?
- Хей, това...
- 3-D телевизор.
- Не...
- Имам 3-D TV.
- Сериозно?
- Боже.
- Успях, човече.
Какво?
Да започваме.
Боже, приятел.
Това е лулата на Гандалф Сивия.
Така е.
Здравей, малък хобит.
- Запали ми ганджата.
- Да.
Аз съм добре известен хомосексуалист адвокат.
Очите ми се чувстват
като че ли се топят.
Трябва ми почивка.
Знаеш ли какво?
Скоро трябва да отидем в къщата на Франко.
Прави парти по случай откриването.
Завърши строежа на къщата си.
Още не съм я виждал, но
се очертава да е супер.
Не съм идвал тук от година
и дойдох да разпусна с теб.
Може да разпуснем заедно,
също така можем и с другите хора.
Като екип.
- Ще познавам ли някого?
- Познаваш Джеймс Франко.
- Той дори не ми знае името.
- Джона Хил.
Не го понасям, и той мен.
Той е най-добричкия човек на света!
Много те харесва.
Той специално говори за
това как той те харесва.
От нищото, той просто каза:
"Знаеш ли какво? Джей е вдъхновение."
Няма как да го е казал.
Също така, просто не мога да го трая.
- Добре, хубаво. Крейг Робинсън.
- Не го знам.
Забавен е.
Много се поти, но е супер човек.
Ще е весело.
Отивам само заради теб.
Обещавам, че ще стоя
при теб цяла нощ, окей?
Няма да те зарежа.
Не, защото искам да съм с тебе през цялото време.
И знаеш ли защо още?
'Щот никой не поставя Джей в ъгъла.
Екстра.
- Мерси.
- Мерси. Ето така.
- Благодаря много, а?
- Благодаря много.
Добре, брат.
Мамка му.
Това е откачено!
- Нали?
- Да бе, нали?
- Гледай само.
- Малко в повече е.
Не мисля така.
Мисля, че си струва парите.
Той да не е Пабло Ескобар, бе?
Стига, човече, това е страхотна улица.
Чанинг Тейтъм живее тук.
За бога...
Ще спреш ли да говориш за...
Това е най-секси улицата в Америка.
- Ти и Чанинг Тейтъм.
- Мисля, че е привлекателен.
- Мисля, че е готина къщата.
- Знам.
Нямам търпение да я видя отвътре.
Затова съм нетърпелив.
Да! Как е човече? Сет!
- Много се радвам, че си тук.
- Радвам се да съм тук.
Хей, Джони, как е?
- Джей.
- Казва се Джей.
Повече няма да го забравя!
Радвам се да те видя.
- Радвам се много. Влезте.
- Да, страхотно.
Гледай. Новата ми къща!
Супер е!
По мой дизайн.
Много готино. Това място е красиво, човек.
Като част от мен е.
Вие двамата току що влязохте в мен.
Позволи ни да се изпразним в теб.
Черешката на тортата. Вижте ги.
Сам ги рисувах.
Рамо до рамо. Отбор.
Леле мале!
Странно ли е?
- Не.
- Сигурен ли си?
Харесва ми много!
Какво мислиш, Джей?
Не съм човек на изкуството.
Не ти харесва?
Хайде...
- Играеш игри нали?
- Да.
- Е, познай какво, приятел? Харесваш изкуството.
- Дам.
- Ходил ли си в Събуей?
- Да.
Да си поръчаш сандвич?
Някой го събира за теб, човече.
Това е изкуство.
Художник на сандвичи.
- Така че, нека ти кажа нещо, Джей.
- Мамка му.
На майка ти оная работа е платното,
а на баща ти пишката е четката.
Бум. Ти си изкуството.
- Мерси, Джеймс Франко.
- Разбра го.
- Сет!
- Минди, здравей.
- Боже, страхотно е да те видя.
- Така е.
Мина много време. Как върви?
- Познаваш ли Джей?
- Не мисля, че съм те срещала на живо.
Беше много добър в "Момиче за милиони".
Това е страхотно.
Благодаря, че го каза.
О боже мой,
ако не изчукам Майкъл Сера довечера,
- ще си пръсна главата.
- Моля?
Бледолик, 50 кила
без косми, сигурно има голям чеп,
надрусан...
Можеш по-добре. Това са си проблеми.
Ри-ри, ами ти,
някога ходиш ли на психиатър?
- Това не е готино.
- Не ми пипай дупето, кучко.
- Майкъл, това не е готино.
- Защо не млъкнеш, Джейсън!
Играем си.
Кажи зеле, бейби.
- Как е, приятел?
- Как е при теб, човече?
Радвам се да те видя.
- Това Джей Барушел ли е?
- Здравей.
Боже, ела тук, човече.
- Как е, Джона?
- Как е при теб?
- Добре. Как си?
- Боже.
- Добре дошъл обратно.
- Благодаря много.
- Кога пристигна?
- Тази сутрин,
и боже, колко ме болят ръцете.
Това е супер.
- Мерси.
- Супер.
И какво правехте?
Мотаехме се цял ден.
Ядохме малко мръсни бургери,
изпушихме яко трева
и играхме на видео игри.
Тревата е яко нещо. Страхотно.
Това е страхотно. Тревата е страхотна.
Беше като
голф серията на Тюлените.
- Страшна препратка.
- Мерси.
Винаги си ги казвал готини.
Всеки го знае.
- Мерси много!
- Завиждам ти.
Веднага щях да дойда,
но осинових този
невъздържан шпаньол.
Красива душичка е.
- Казва се Аджа.
- Аджа?
- Да.
- Как е буква по буква?
- А-Д-Ж-А.
- A-Д...
Искате ли да видите снимка?
- Много е мила.
- Хей!
Само погледнете.
Не може да лае.
Не знае как, така че...
- Не знае?
- Не знае...
и се опитах да я науча,
обаче тя някак си крещи,
и се беше изправила,
със муцуна забита в клетката,
и правеше...
Да, готино.
Момчета, да ви кажа, пуши ми се,
така че отивам да намеря някой,
от когото да взема цигара, става ли?
- Това е яко, човече. Харесваш ми.
- Мерси, подобно.
Окей, да се върнеш.
Ще се върна.
Добре, момчета.
Пич. Знам.
Мисля че прогресираме.
- Tова беше много добро.
- И честно казано, той е твой стар приятел.
- Ние сме новите ти. Той се чувства застрашен.
- Да, човек.
Разбирам.
Всичко ще бъде наред.
И честно си мисля, че тази вечер,
ще наредим нещата.
Щастлив съм.
Обаче е едно и също нещо много пъти.
ТВ жената ми отваря хладилника,
и почва:
"Какво стана с тортата?"
И аз се показвам с малко глазура
и викам:
"Ква торта, бе?"
-'Щот си я изял!
- Да.
'Щото си изял тортата!
"Все пак е моя рожден ден."
Ето заради това си номер едно.
- Ти си Джей нали?
- Да.
- Момчето на Сет?
- Аха.
- Как я караш? Радвам се да те видя.
- Добре. И аз теб.
- Аз съм Крейг. Това е Ема.
- Здрасти. Здравей.
Идваш в града на гости при него или?
Да само за малко, сещате се.
Опитвам се да не идвам тук често.
Не ми харесва много.
- Не ти харесва ЛА?
- Не съм много по начина на живот тук.
А по какъв си падаш?
Виж го. Той е като хипстър, нали?
Не, не съм.
Да, изглежда, че мразиш много неща
и долнището ти е ужасно стегнато.
Не, просто... не харесвам Лос Анджелис.
Това не ме прави хипстър.
На бас, че мразиш филми, харесвани
от всички хора.
- Аз не...
- Харесваш ли Форест Гъмп?
Не, не, това е ужасно лайно.
"Животът е като кутия бонбони", не?
Да, запознат съм с филма.
"Не знаеш какво ще ти се падне."
Защо не направим продължение
на Ананас Експрес?
- С удоволствие бих направил.
- Имаш ли идеи или?
- Да.
- Каква?
Че Ред, Дани става нарко бос
сещаш се, след като убихме другия
и иска да убие Уди Харелсън,
защото той ще направи реч,
която ще легализира тревата,
ефективно отказваща наркобароните
от бизнеса.
- Страхотно!
- Да страхотно е!
Но още не...
Не знаем как да свърши.
Аз знам.
- Дани се опитва да ни убие.
- Да.
И аз се жертвам за теб.
И той ме убива,
и се жертвам за теб.
И Дани ме изяжда.
- Защо?
- Не знам.
Опитвам се да измисля
най-гадния начин.
Да, може да те изяде. Добра идея.
Полудял е. Ще ме изяде.
- Хей, Крис.
- Как е?
Хей, този кокаин мирише ли ти странно?
- Мамка му!
- Майкъл, какво по дяволите, човек?
Скъпо е това, копеле!
Какво правиш?
Преди не съм опитвал кокаин, човек...
Еми, направи най-готиния първи път...
-'щот тва е много готин...
- Боже, боже, нервен съм, пич.
- Не знам какво...
- Какво ти е, човече?
- Виж, тоя се побърква.
- О боже.
Преди не съм пробвал тоя
шибан наркотик.
Майк, моля те!
Ще ти помогна да преминеш.
- Майк, никой...
- Ще ти бъда водач.
Добре си, Крис, добре си.
- Започва се...
Имаш малко по мустаците, бейби...
- Ти какво... Майкъл!
Сега, момчета, искам да сте много секси.
Ще пеем на момичетата.
Всички момчета, почвайте да пеете
със глас стил Бари Уайт.
Свали си гащичките,
Хайде, Риана!
Свали си гащичките за мен.
Хайде, Крейг.
Може ли да го духаш, за мен?
Ще направя едно от тези неща.
Като ангел.
Ами собственика?
Нямам гащи!
Той няма гащи, всички!
Нямаме гащи,
Никой няма гащи!
Няма друго парти, като това без гащи!
'Щот това парти няма край!
Майната им на гащите!
Майната им...
Кое не е безопасно за деца?
- Има доста остри ръбове.
- Остри.
Ще си разбие главата
в едно от тези.
Дете може да падне от този
шибан парапет.
То за това е
там, за да не падне.
- Хей, извинете.
- Искам да имам деца един ден.
- Хей, Джей.
- О, здрасти Джона.
Има ли място наоколо, където
мога да си купя цигари?
Да.
Има едно място, на четири преки
от тук, може би.
Искаш ли да дойдеш с мен?
Дай ми ето толкова време.
Толкова джойнт време.
- Исусе!
- Хей, Джей!
Хей, трябва ли ти тоалетна?
Давай.
Не,... съжалявам.
Кой иска малко?
Добре ли си, човек?
Няма нищо. Просто, знаеш ли,
веднага след като пристигнахме
ти направи това, което каза, че няма да правиш.
- Кое?
- Заряза ме.
Не съм. Шегуваш ли се?
Не съм те зарязал.
Говорихме с Джона, и ти отиде за цигара.
Е, нали знаеш, че това беше извинение.
Излезнах, защото Джона беше задник.
Не е вярно.
Ако нещо, ти се държеше като задник.
Джона е най-добрия тип, човече.
О, Боже мой, това
е тънък фурнир на доброта.
Няма друг толкова добър.
Джона е толкова добър.
Убийците са толкова добри.
Отговори ми на един въпрос.
Дупето на Майкъл Сера толкова
хубаво ли е, колкото си го представях?
Боже господи...
Представям си го като поничка,
малка поръсена поничка.
Толкова е светло тук.
Супер светло е.
Много съм напушен.
Толкова вкусни неща.
Кое да избера?
Ще взема нещо за пиене.
- Добре.
Извинете, възможно ли ще бъде
дъщеря ми да използва тоалетната?
Спешно е.
Прочетете табелата. Само за клиенти.
Сериозно ли?
Защо си мислиш, че е там, а?
Спокойно, татко. Ще стискам.
Нека просто да купим нещо за майка ти.
Еми, предполагам, че трябва, нали?
Тази касиерка е лоша.
Разтревожих се. Купи това вместо мен.
Не мога да правя това напушен.
Мисля, че ще се върна у вас.
Не ми харесва при Франко.
Пич, искам да се запознаеш с тези хора.
Друг начин няма да има
ако не положиш усилия.
Не ми харесва там.
Искам само да пия и да пуша трева.
Ами...
Ами аз?
Добре ли си?
Видя ли това?
Какво по дяволите?
- О, Боже, Исусе!
- Бягай!
- Насам!
- Добре!
Боже!
Господи.
Бягай!
Исусе Христе!
Защо ме доведе тук?
- Какво по дяволите, Сет?
- Не знам какво става!
- Връщаме се при Франко.
- Защо?
Просто бягай!
Леле мале!
Връщаме се!
Мамка му.
- Боже!
Почти стигнахме!
Хей, добре ли сте?
Добре ли сте?
Имаше земетресение. Вие
усетихте ли го?
- Беше лудница.
- По дяволите, не.
Тук не се чувства нищо.
Това място е крепост.
Това не беше земетресение.
- Беше много по-лудо.
- Не...
Какво по-лудо има?
Имаше лъчове от небето,
вдигащи хората във въздуха.
Той е на наркотици.
Стига, хора, не се заяждайте с него.
Той е добра душа.
За какво говореше?
Имаше хора, вдигнати във въздуха.
- Джей.
- Вдигнати във въздуха ли?
Тук никой не беше вдигнат.
На мен ми беше вдигнат.
Окей, питайте Сет. Той беше там...
Кажи им.
Сет, за какво по дяволите говори?
Нямам идея, честно.
Вдигна ли се някой във въздуха?
Не съм видял. Не знам за какво говори.
Беше с мен, какви ги говориш?
Всички хора с нас в магазина
изчезнаха!
Не видях синя светлина,
изсмукваща хора в небето.
Звучиш налудничаво, човек...
Трябва да сме щастливи, че...
Не е свършило!
- Всичко е наред, споко!
Само лек трус. Партито продължава
Камионите идват след 10 минути.
Да!
- Животински стил!
Леле мале!
- Тръгвайте!
- Движение!
Бързо!
- Тук е безопасно.
Не е безопасно, бе!
Крейг, какво правиш?
- Това е земетресение!
- Мамка му!
Хайде, движение!
- Махни ми се от пътя!
Боже мой, Сет!
- Мамка му!
Сет!
- Какво по дяволите?
Не стъпвайте всички по тревата!
Какво по дяволите?
Боже!
Какво се случва, за бога?
- Пол!
Какво става?
Добре, всички. Чуйте ме.
Кой ми взе телефона, човек?
Мартин, изпразни си джобовете!
- Какво?
Видях те в тоалетната, човече.
Наберете ми телефона!
Тихо! Не мога да повярвам!
Неприемливо е това, след целия
този кокаин, който хвърлих за вас.
- Хвърлих го!
- Не съм ти взел телефона!
-310...
- Майк, Майк...
Лицето ми!
Какво става с мен?
Леле!
Боже, това е срамно.
Риана!
Дай ми крак, моля те!
Боже!
Крейг, помощ, губя захват!
Късно е, вече си в дупката!
- За какво говориш?
- Махни ми се от пътя!
Извинявай.
Кейрън!
Сет, хайде! Влез в къщата!
Хайде, Сет!
Боже, ще умра!
Мартин!
- Боже!
- Кевин!
Какво по дяволите?
Боже, махни се от мен Азиз!
Майната ти, Кевин!
Боже, махни си ръцете от мен!
Махни си...
Не!
Не мога да издържам вече!
Трябва да се протегнеш и да ме хванеш!
Добре, хвани ме за ръката и ще
те издърпам!
Сигурен ли си? Ще ти приложа
цялата си тежест!
Ще се протегна, ясно?!
- Да!
Сигурен ли си, че ще можеш?
Ще те хвана на 3
Едно, две, три!
Добре, приятел.
Сега ще те залюлея.
- Държа те приятел.
Же държиш цялата ми тежест!
- Добре, хайде.
- Можеш ли?
- Мога!
Не искам да умра!
- Добре.
Едно, две... три!
Не!
Не! Не!
О, човече.
Мамка му.
Какво стана?
Джей! Жив си!
Слава богу!
- Не съм мъртъв още!
Казах ви да стоите вътре
Какво стана току що?
- Боже всички са мъртви!
Казах ви да не излизате!
- Всички сте прави?
Опитах се да спася Азиз!
- Даде най-доброто от себе си! Обичам те!
Защо избягахте навън?
Знаеш ли какво, Джеймс?
Спри да викаш.
Откачаш, Джей!
Може би съм малко откачил също!
Той не е толкова силен, като теб!
- Те паднаха!
Виж ми къщата!
- Опитах се да ги спася! Всички паднаха!
Махни си ръцете, Джона!
Може ли да дадем на Джей малко вода?
Трябва му хидратация!
- Водата не работи!
Всички тичат...
Телефона ми замря.
Хора, интернета не работи!
Нека включим телевизията.
Къде е телевизора?
В пода е.
- В пода?
Това е яко.
- Да.
Много готино.
Впечетляващо, Джеймс.
Най-голямото земетресение в Лос...
Полицаите казват, да си останете
по домовете.ю.
И също така съобщения за грабежи и бунтове
се разпространяват из целия град.
Бунтове.
Полицията е превъзхождана по количество
и хората си помагат.
Обявено е военно положение..
Еър Форс Едно падна...
Мамка му. Край, хора!
Еми мисля, че трябва...
Трябва да се върнем у вас, а?
За какво говориш?
Няма начин. Не излизам от тук!
Не искам да умра
в дома на Джеймс Франко!
Чу телевизора.
Каза да седим по домовете.
Трябва да седим, докато не започнат
с спасяванията!
При голямо земетресение, кого спасяват
първо?
Актьорите, известните.
Ще качат Клуни, Сандра Бълок, аз...
и ако има място
и вие можете да дойдете.
Важното е, че ние ще се измъкнем първи.
Какво беше това?
- Вече става лудница навън, хора!
We can't leave. I'm not leaving, okay?
I'm a victim.
I've had a victim's mentality my whole life.
People can smell it on me.
When I was a kid,
I had man-titties.
The bullies held me down,
they tittie-fucked me.
That's what's happening out there right now.
That's right, we are all soft.
- Yeah.
- We are all soft!
We are actors!
We pretend to be hard, man.
- Yeah.
- We soft as baby shit.
As baby shit, soft as...
Wait, Craig, what are you doing, man?
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing to the painting, man?
- We got to board this shit up, man.
- Board it up?
We got to protect ourselves. We don't know
-how long we gonna be in here.
- Okay, chill.
There's raccoons, and bandits,
and shit out there.
- This is Obey, man!
- If you get out the way!
This is my favorite fucking painting!
What are you doing, Craig?
Guys, help.
Help. Help. Get off.
Chill. Look.
Helicopter! Helicopter!
The good guys are here.
We're fine! It's gonna be fine.
God damn!
Shit!
- You okay?
- No, I'm not okay!
Fuck your house, Franco!
My house didn't do that!
You don't got a tool kit or nothing?
Just a toolbox?
I don't know. Look in there.
Where's the edge of this shit?
Your thumb's in my butthole, man.
Y'all need this dick?
No, we're not using it.
All right, I'm gonna take it over here.
- Careful with that dick.
- Damn.
It's heavy.
There it is, got that dick now.
That dick is coming now.
Yeah, got this big dick.
Hey, hey.
- What now?
- Listen.
Not the Rogen, all right?
Don't take him.
Take me.
We got 12 bottles of water,
four whiskeys, six bottles of wine,
tequila, Nutella,
cheese, pizza, eggs, bananas,
apples, bacon, steaks,
pancake mix, CT Crunch, milk,
ketchup, a Milky Way,
half ounce Sour Diesel,
three and a half grams Grand Master Kush,
one ounce of 'shrooms, 15 pills of ecstasy,
a porno mag, a baseball bat,
and the video camera
from the movie 27 Hours.
127 Hours.
And a functioning revolver
from the movie Flyboys.
Old Faithful.
- Jesus.
- Thing's real.
- No, I kept this from the movie.
- Yeah.
- This is an actual revolver.
- I see.
Franco, that's very uncomfortable.
Could you put that down, please?
Loaded.
- Loveit
- Awesome.
- Can you just put the gun away?
- I always keep my props.
- That's really cool.
- Always keep my props.
I know how to handle it.
He knows what he's doing. I like this bit.
I like it. I get it. Let me see.
- It's real. It's heavy.
- Let me see it like that.
- God damn!
- Come on, guys!
- You could kill...
- Careful.
- Bang,bang!
- Jesus!
- Please, put it down!
- Fuck!
Bang, bang, bang. You're dead.
- I hope you're fucking happy.
- Pow, pow, pow.
Stop... Guys, stop fucking with the gun.
- Jesus!Jesus!
- Pow, pow.
- It's a real gun!
- Bang.
It's so funny.
- Guys, it's funny.
-It's not funny!
We're getting sidetracked.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- I'll just kill myself.
- No!
- Don't do that, Jonah!
-Jesus.
- Oh, no.
- Jonah, give it back.
- I don't know! I don't know.
- Don't do that.
- Jonah.
- I'm so...
- Oh, my God. Hey.
- Oh, dude.
- Come on, no, no. Don't. Jesus!
- Would you put the thing down?
The whole...
I'm trying to have some fun, man.
Okay, okay, Jesus.
Look, just because a bunch
of people fell into a hole outside
doesn't mean we can't have some fun.
We're a bunch of best friends hanging out.
It's like a sleepover.
Okay, food.
How are we gonna deal with this?
Can I have that Milky Way?
No, you can't have the Milky Way.
- That's my Milky Way.
- There's a bunch... What?
I went out this morning,
specifically bought this Milky Way
to eat after my party.
- That's weird.
-It's not weird. It's my special food.
I like it. Back
me up on that, Seth.
I don't think you should get
the whole Milky Way.
I want some of the Milky Way.
I'd be pretty bummed if I don't
at least get a bite of the Milky Way.
Now Craig wants a
bite of the Milky Way.
Yeah, I want a bite of the Milky Way.
It's a fucking Milky Way.
A fifth of everything
is what's fair and reasonable.
Everyone gets a fifth of everything.
I want one-fifth of your T-shirt!
I want the bottom part, the belly.
I'm not sporting a
crop top in your house.
I'll cut that shit
off and make a headband.
You couldn't handle my midriff.
Guys, the only issue is,
I kind of need the Milky Way.
For fuck's sake.
No, for real, I have low blood sugar,
and if my endorphins drop too low,
I'm gonna be a nightmare to be around.
- What?
- Your LBS starts acting up,
you can have a finger scoop of Nutella,
okay?
- One finger scoop of Nutella.
- Fair.
I'm going to bed.
Jesus fucking...
Don't touch that Milky Way, Jonah.
Night, James.
Oh, God, no!
Fuck.
-Hey.
I'm gonna sleep with you.
- What?
- I'm gonna sleep with you.
- It's too scary to sleep alone.
- But this is my little area.
Well, I'm invading your little area.
I'm sorry, but I'm too scared, okay?
Are you mad at me, man?
If I was pissed at you,
I'm sure it would have something to do
with the fact that I had no interest
in coming to this house socially,
and now, I am barricaded in here
with a bunch of
people that I really hate.
Maybe this was meant to be.
Maybe this horrible, horrible,
deadly earthquake happened
so we could become closer
as a group of friends.
I don't need a group. I'm like DMX, man.
I'm a lone wolf.
DMX isn't a lone wolf.
DMX has the Ruff Ryder crew.
You can't stop, drop,
and open up shop alone.
You need people to help you
in an earthquake disastery situation.
It was something else.
It was Judgment Day.
Like Terminator 2?
No, not like Terminator 2.
For God's sakes.
Like Skynet? You think this is Skynet?
- Like, Skynet went live?
- No.
Will you please stop saying "Skynet"?
Well, you're the one that said Judgment Day.
The biblical Judgment Day.
- What?
- That's crazy. It's just...
- You fucking heathen.
- Okay, here's the thing.
Let's say for a second there was blue light
sucking people up into the sky.
That means that we were not
awesome enough to go to heaven.
Shit! Shit.
What y'all doing?
Fuck you, Craig.
I'm scared. It's scary by myself.
It's way better with more people.
- I'm gonna come down here.
- Yeah, good, yeah. Get in here, man.
Get right in there.
So, you're gonna...
- Right here.
I feel better, actually. I like that.
It's better with more people.
Hey, guys--
- Jesus Christ.
- Jesus!
Sorry. Franco has this crazy open floor plan.
I can hear every word you guys are saying.
I might as well hang with you guys
if that's cool.
- Nice.
- Coming in hot.
I gonna grab a blanket from you.
Give me that blanket.
- Get in the middle of it.
- That's good.
- That's it.
-It feels so much more safe now, guys.
It's nice here.
- Should we spoon it?
- Yeah, you want to?
- No!
- Want to go...
- Dick to butt?
- No.
- My butt to you and then Jay.
- I don't want to butt to dick to anything.
Are you docking into me?
You're doing tip to me?
- Or what are you doing?
- Should we go butt to butt or dick to...
Seth and I are gonna go ass to ass.
Do you want to go front to front?
- No, I'm fine just going dicks up.
-Dic:ks up?
- I think I'm going dick to ass.
- You know what?
I'm going Scarf ace-style.
- Both of you guys.
- Wait, yeah.
- There we go.
- Yeah.
This is the best way.
Good night, boys.
- Good night.
Good night, guys.
- Night, my sweet guys.
- Good night.
Sweet dreams, fellas.
Fuck,yeah.
Franco! Good morning, sunshine.
Guys! Guys! Wake up!
Danny's alive!
He's eating all the fucking food!
- No!
- Danny, man, don't.
Danny!
No, it's cool, man.
I fucking made this for you guys.
- Stop eating!
- Don't eat another piece of bacon.
Guys, just chill the fuck out, okay?
I'm sure the Green Goblin
can fucking afford some more bacon.
Dude, that shit's supposed to last us
till we get rescued!
Wait a second.
I know what happened.
You guys dropped acid, didn't you?
Craig doesn't have any pants on.
He got fucking wild.
Probably danced, sweated all over the place.
You got white shit
all over your mouth, Franco.
You probably sucked somebody's dick.
Jonah over here probably watched
and jerked off.
Jay, I didn't even know you were in town.
Good to see you.
Danny, we're not on acid.
We didn't suck each other's dicks!
James Franco didn't suck
any dick last night?
Now I know y'all are tripping.
You actually not know
what happened last night?
Daniel, you may want
to stay seated for a second.
Some really messed-up stuff happened,
and there were a lot of fatalities.
Really? You're putting your serious voice on,
Jonah?
Okay, tell me about these "fatalities."
Dude, Segel's dead, Krumholtz
is dead, Michael Cera's dead.
Guess if Michael Cera's gone,
it's not a total loss, huh?
- Jesus, Danny.
- Michael Cera's dead.
- What?
-It's not like that.
- It's not funny, man.
-It's really not funny.
Seth, that's a better performance
than you've given in your last six movies.
Where the fuck was that
in Green Hornet, huh?
Jonah, you're fucking sucking balls.
You're an Academy Award nominated person.
You need to be fucking
selling that shit, dude.
"Fatalities. There were some fatalities."
Fatalities.
Okay, now that was good.
That was good.
Does it seem like we're fucking joking?
Hey, hey, hey!
What the fuck you eating, man?
Spit it out your mouth.
Give me the bacon!
Shit.
Shit, what do we do?
Shoot 'em! Shoot 'em! Shoot 'em!
Should I shoot?
- Shut up, Franco!
- Shoot the door, Franco!
Oh, God!
Did you not hear me knocking out here?
I've been knocking forever.
Please! Please!
You've got to let me in!
- Hang on a second.
- What?
Guys, I know it sounds really weird,
but I don't think we should let him in.
Why not?
Yeah, why not?
I can hear you, by the way.
I'm sorry. We just don't know you, man.
You could be like, a looter,
or a rapist, or a tittie-fucker.
Like, I'm sorry.
Look, guys, we just boarded up
this whole house to keep everyone out,
and the first guy comes to the door,
we're gonna let him in?
I mean, how do we know
we can trust this guy?
I want to live!
Things have gone crazy out here!
"Fucking crazy out here!"
This guy fucking sucks.
- What if he's the rapist?
- Man, even if he is a rapist,
-he can't rape all of us.
- Yeah! No! So I'm not...
- I'm not a rapist!
- You want to tittie-fuck us?
If you want me to tittie-fuck you, I will!
So good! You'll love it.
Seth, back me up, please.
We can't just leave him out there to die.
Are you crazy?
What do you want to do?
I'll do whatever you want to do.
Let's vote on it.
Yeah, I fucking vote you let me in.
Here's my vote. Fuck all of you.
I'm letting him in. This is boring.
There's something out here!
This is real! This is fucking real!
God damn it!
You guys!
This man was alive a few seconds ago.
We can't play soccer with his head!
Pick it up, Jonah!
What the fuck is going on?
He blinked at me.
- He blinked at my face.
- Seth, put it over there.
Oh, my God!
I got it. I got it, guys.
There's blood all over my floor!
Time to relax for a second.
Okay, someone should look out the hole.
I ain't looking out that hole!
Last person looked through that hole
got his head chopped off!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Whatever is out there might still be out there.
Okay, I know, I know.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
There's a lookout!
Jesus Christ! Look, there's
a huge fucking hole down there!
What the fuck is this?
- Where's the thing that killed the guy?
- I don't know.
- How'd his head fall off?
- And where's the rest of him?
Hi.
This is James Franco,
in my house, in my library.
We've been stuck here for about 24 hours.
Danny McBride is here.
I didn't even invite him to my party,
but he came and
passed out in the bathtub,
and I got to say
it's, like, typical fucking McBride.
Like, I've been feeling really weird
about him lately.
Like, I don't really know
if I want to be friends with him,
and then he fucking
showed up at my party,
and now, we're stuck here with him
in disaster lockdown, so...
- What up? What's going on?
-Hey, Danny. What's up, man?
Not much. What are you doing?
What is this?
It's just a video confessional.
Fuck that dude.
- Earthquakes cause tsunamis.
- Yes.
Tsunamis cause other tsunamis, disaster.
I mean, for all we know,
the fucking Lakers could have just won,
and that's the reason
why all this is happening.
Hole in Franco's front yard? Sinkhole.
Every single time I turn on the news,
sinkhole in South America.
Bunch of South Americans
getting sucked into the ground.
- Sinkhole de Mayo.
That's why it's named that,
because sinkholes happen
in the summertime.
It's not wildfires. It's not earthquakes.
It's not sinkholes.
- I think I know what it is.
- Let's hear it.
I think it's the Apocalypse.
What?
I'm serious, boys.
It's all in here, in the Book of Revelations.
- You took my Bible?
- Well, just hear me out,
and you tell me that what I'm describing
isn't what's going on right now.
"And the skies shall open up,
and the light of the Lord shall shine down,
"and those of good heart shall be brought
into my kingdom of heaven."
That's the Rapture,
those are the gigantic beams of blue light.
"And there will be a great
mountain burning in fire."
I mean, the Hollywood Hills
are literally engulfed in flames
as we sit here right now.
The Hollywood Hills ain't no mountain.
It's a hill.
Takes about 10 minutes to get across
that motherfucker with no traffic.
- Coldwater.
- I take Laurel Canyon.
- Cahuenga.
- I usually zip down Barham.
- Boys, can I just fucking finish?
I love Laurel Canyon.
"And out of the pit
rose a great red dragon having seven heads,
"that old serpent called the devil and Satan,
"which deceiveth the whole world,
was released onto the earth."
I love that dude.
He's from Where the Wild Things Are.
-It's a load of bullshit.
-It's not bullshit.
Want to know something else, Jay?
If this is the end of the world,
and all the good people died,
what you're saying is
Seth, me, Jonah, Craig and Danny
are a bunch of assholes.
I'm straight-up lovable, son.
And if this really is the Apocalypse,
you're here too.
So, that means you're just
as shitty as the rest of us.
Doesn't feel too good, does it?
Hey, guys. I'm going to sleep now.
Nobody come in here and bother me.
Go fish.
Put it back inside of here.
- Do you know what it is?
- Yeah.
Now you ask me
for something that you need.
First bit.
You're not cutting it all?
That's smart. You're divvying it up first.
- This is like, Fruyére or some shit.
- That's me.
Come on, Danny!
- You licked your finger.
- Come on, man.
If they're all equal, what does it matter?
Keep your hands and fingers off.
- Seth?
- Yeah.
- Can I talk to you for a second?
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, no shit.
Here. Off the menu, my man.
Holy shit, man.
Where did you get these?
Hey, what's cheese without a few crackers?
Know what I'm saying?
- Hide it.
- Okay.
-'Cause we're a team.
Freaks forever, brother.
Let's do all the drugs.
I don't really want to.
Should have thought of that
before you drank a can full of ecstasy.
What?
Should we call Red?
Get more weed?
I don't know, man.
That guy's gone crazy.
Good thing I have a lot
of fucking weed for you guys.
I hooked you guys UP-
Now I need you guys
to assassinate Woody Harrelson.
If pot's legalized, my business will suffer.
And if my business suffers, I suffer.
So much suffering.
All 'cause of that inbred hemp seed,
Woody Harrelson.
I have to do what's right.
Weed is for the people.
It's the people's weed.
- If you don't assassinate him...
-We already quit.
...I'm gonna assassinate both of you.
"Run!
"Go!
B.F.F.F.F.F.F.F.F.F.
F. forever.
B.F.F.F.F.F.F.F.F.F.F.
- Look out!
-Shit!
You're letting them get away!
I smoked weed with Steve Jobs,
and that's when he
came up with the iPad.
It's pretty great.
We should make sequels
to more of our movies.
Yeah!
How 'bout we not do Your Highness 2?
- Yeah.
- Do 128 Hours.
- The beginning of the rest of your comedies.
- Looks good.
Oh, my God!
- Emma!
-It's Emma.
Oh, my God, you guys are alive.
You're actually alive. Thank God!
I hid in a drainpipe for days.
Like, three or four.
I don't even know how many.
And then I stopped hearing people,
and I started hearing growling noises.
Out there, in your travels,
did you see anything
that you would describe
as Apocalyptish?
I mean, no,
but I would say it's completely obvious
what's going on here.
I mean, it's a zombie invasion.
- Fuck!
- I'm the one who said it's been zombies.
- You said zombies?
- I said zombies the whole time.
- I don't think... You never said zombies.
Wait a second.
You guys haven't been proven right.
These are still just theories.
Honestly, I'm just so relieved
that you guys are here,
and I'm very happy
about the idea of sleeping and just...
- You tired?
- Yeah.
If you want to take a little rest,
you're welcome to do that upstairs.
- Thank you.
- Cool.
- I'll show you the way.
- Thank you.
Thanks, guys.
Seriously, you're awesome, really.
You're awesome.
So fucking tight.
We'll be right out here, okay?
Fuck are you guys doing out here?
Here's what I think we should do.
She's British, right?
She's used to eating shitty food anyway.
Let's just give her all the shitty food
that we don't want.
That's fucked up.
Look how tiny she is.
She's not even a full seven.
She's, like, half a seven.
This is a fucking cool thing, man.
I, for one, am very excited.
I'm a massive Harry Potter fan.
- What?
- Yes. I love fucking Harry Potter.
I cannot wait till she wakes up and I can
ask her all these amazing questions about
how they made those motion pictures.
Take it easy, Dumbledore.
Guys, listen, listen. I think we need
to address the elephant in the room.
Whoa. Jay, don't talk about Craig like that.
- That's fucked up. I'm right here, man.
- Yeah.
I'm not calling Craig an elephant.
- Wow, that's fucking weird.
- What does that even mean?
- Yeah, no.
- That's racist.
I wasn't referring to him.
I was referring to the issue
that's on all of our minds.
What?
This is one girl in
a house with six males.
Yeah. Really safe.
Ideal scenario.
She's like a little sister.
I think that she needs...
It's important that she feels safe.
- Yeah.
- And comfortable.
And we should be mindful.
Who's making her not feel safe?
Well, I'm just saying, we should...
We don't want to
give off a bad vibe.
- Vibe?
- Vibes? I ain't giving no vibes.
Yeah, wait, what kind of vibes
are you talking about, man?
He's talking about us
giving off a rapey vibe.
- Hey!
- What?
- Jesus.
- Jay, what the fuck, man?
Chill out, dude.
- Why you putting that shit in the mix?
- Yeah.
- He fucking said it.
- You're the one saying it.
No one here is thinking about raping anyone.
Well, you talking about vibes
is the only thing that's rapey
going on right now.
Dude, nothing was rapey till
you brought up the rapey vibes.
- Fucking one who smelt it dealt it, dawg.
- True that, dude.
One who denies it supplies it.
I know, it's farts, I get it.
Guys, guys, guYs-
Jay's not rapey.
Jay couldn't rape a fly.
He probably could.
Maybe we should just stop this
entire conversation right now.
If anyone's gonna rape anyone here,
it's probably gonna be Danny.
- What the fuck, Franco?
- What?
Why do you think I'm gonna rape somebody?
I'm just trying to lay it out there.
I'm not gonna rape anyone, all right?
If anyone's gonna rape somebody, it's Jay.
- What?
- He came up with the rape idea.
And his face looks like the police sketch
-of a fucking rapist.
- True.
What the fuck does that mean?
If anybody's raping Emma Watson,
it's fucking Sir Rapes-a-Lot over here.
- Chill out.
- Hey!
Easy. Easy.
Back the fuck up!
- Emma.
- What's wrong?
- Wait, what's wrong?
I just heard you guys talking about
which one of you is gonna get to rape me.
No,no,no,no!
Guys, I got it. I got it.
No. It's funny. It's funny.
We were specifically talking
about not raping you.
- Jesus!
- Holy shit!
Back up!
It's me, Jonah!
It's me, Jonah Hill.
America's sweetheart. J-bug, J-bone.
- Your friend. I would never hurt you.
- Get back!
Give me everything you have to drink!
Put it in the bag!
There's six of us.
You cannot rob us!
I'm not fucking around!
Give her drinks!
Put the drinks in a bag!
- Oh, God.
- Get all the drinks in a bag!
Hurry the fuck up!
Okay, they're getting the drinks.
- Put the ax down.
- Don't give the Milky Way away.
All right, you can
put the ax down now.
Now, Franco! Shoot her face!
Shoot her!
I'm not gonna shoot Emma Watson!
Look, Emma, just stay here with us.
It's a lot safer than out there.
Hermione just stole all of our shit.
Little bitty-ass 20-year-old jacked us.
And then Jay suggested that we all rape her,
and now she's gone.
I didn't... I was just... I...
I think the only reason why
he did that is because Jay knows
he's about fucking two minutes away
from becoming the house bitch himself.
So now, motherfuckers is thirsty.
All right, guys-
The door to the basement's out there,
around the side of the house.
I know for sure there's at least
two jugs of water.
Okay.
Any volunteers?
Does anyone want to volunteer
and go with Jay?
What?
I thought you said, "Someone volunteer
to go with me out there."
I must have misheard you.
- I'm sorry.
- You did not, you motherfucker.
Hey, okay, ease up.
Just chill out, dude.
Just relax, man. God.
So how we gonna decide this, fellas?
All right, guys, it's simple.
Whoever pulls the burnt match
has to go get the water.
Who wants to go first?
I'll do it.
Craig.
All right.
Go ahead, brother.
No whammies, no whammies.
- Hey, hey.
- Yes! Yeah!
_Fu°k,ye$I
'Yés!
Fuck, yes. Fuck, yes.
- So sorry, Craig.
- A lot of guys in here
that I wish it was instead of you.
You want to go
best two out of three?
If I tug, if I pull in anyway,
or if you hear me screaming,
anything, you pull me
right back in, all right?
Yeah. We'll try, man, but you're pretty heavy.
What?
No, I mean, I'm saying,
I just don't think it's smart
-to make any guarantees.
- Fuck,no.
- You promise to pull me back in.
- No, no, we're...
- You got me?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- We're gonna do our best.
- All right.
- You want to do a test run?
- Yeah.
You gotta scream.
Let us hear the scream.
Pull.
Nice. Very nice.
Everyone thank Craig for doing this.
- Thanks, Craig.
- Thank you, Craig.
Go for it, Craig.
Getting smoky in here.
Go, go, go, go.
This is fucked up.
Goddamn.
Smoky as fuck out here.
Rope burn!
Grab it, grab it, grab it!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
- Shit.
- Oh, no.
Shit. Shit.
Come on, motherfucker. Shit!
Fuck this shit.
Fellas, fellas! Pull me in!
Pull the rope!
- Pull me in!
- We don't have the rope anymore!
We fucking dropped it! We're sorry!
You've got the rope, man!
What?
- Craig!
- What the fuck do we do?
Craig! Craig!
Are you okay?
What happened, man?
I don't know! There's something out there.
Oh, shit!
A knife! Somebody throw me a knife!
I'll get it.
- Why?
- OMG.
Jay, I'm so sorry, bro.
The fuck?
Cut it! Cut it! Cut
it! Cut it! Cut it!
God! What the fuck was that?
I don't know what the fuck that was,
but I ain't going back out there.
Craig, you didn't even
get any of the water.
The door was fucked up.
Damn it, this is so frustrating!
It's so close, but so far.
The water, it's, like, right underneath us.
Like, right there.
What do you mean "right underneath us"?
Like, literally, like, right there.
If you went right through the floor.
Yo.
Danny and Jonah's shift ends in ten minutes,
so our break is almost over.
Okay.
Let me ask you something.
You really think this is
the Apocalypse?
You saw something out there, didn't you?
All right, let's just say
for sake of argument, what if I did?
What if this is the real shit,
right now, happening?
What if it is, man?
We're not prepared for this.
- What do we do? What's next?
-It says in the Bible,
"The worthy will ascend to Heaven."
Even if it is
the Apocalypse, it's not the end of us.
There's still hope.
We just have to somehow
try to prove our worthiness.
Okay, so, you mean, like,
like the Ten Commandments,
like, do shit unto people
that'll do the same shit to you.
That's a great place to start.
You know, to just overall love.
Just be nicer
and follow those commandments.
Listen. We're gonna get through this.
We're gonna get through this, man.
You know why?
'Cause we're gonna do it together.
You promise?
We're gonna do this.
I hear everything.
Who did this?
Did what? What are you talking about?
Jizzed all over the pages
of this nice magazine
I was nice enough to tell you about.
Was it you, Seth?
No.
- No?
-It was me, Franco.
I fucking made jizz in your magazine.
- Why?
- When I fucking jack off
long enough, I end upjizzing, dude.
I'm assuming the same shit works for you?
Real fucking smart answer!
Why don't you fucking aim, huh?
I have a particularly explosive ejaculate.
It just goes everywhere.
It's like a fucking wild fireman's hose.
You just got to grab on and pray to God
it doesn't get in your eyes or your mouth.
The fuck kind of jerking off is that?
What, you never had any brothers?
You didn't learn to jizz in a fucking sock
or on a fucking tissue?
No, I don't have any brothers.
I was raised in a house of women!
I highly doubt they fucking taught you
to fucking close your eyes
and fucking cum wherever you want!
I mean, you're getting all worked up
over a fucking porno mag!
Who has goddamn porno mags anymore?
Welcome to the 21st century, Buck Rogers!
You designed a house with
fucking iPads in the walls,
yet you're jerking your dick
like a goddamn pilgrim!
That's right, man.
I like to fucking read!
You think that's the only thing
ljerked off in here?
I've been dropping loads around this
fucking house like a goddamn dump truck.
You don't cum on my stuff!
I'll cum wherever the fuck I want, James.
I'll fucking cum in your kitchen.
I'll cum on your fucking art.
I'll cum anywhere I want!
I will fucking cum right on you!
I will cum like a fucking
madman all over you, McBride!
I fucking wish you'd cum on me right now.
I fucking dare you to cum on me!
God!
I'm gonna jack my dick
so fucking hard in here!
This, no more, man.
All over your fucking face.
This fucking all more.
All over the fucking place!
I'll fucking cum anywhere I want!
I'll fucking cum on these walls!
I'll cum on the fucking cabinets!
On the fucking furniture!
I'll cum everywhere!
If I see your dick one more time,
I'm gonna fucking shoot it off!
You don't have enough bullets, bitch.
No fucking jerking off in my house, McBride!
- Come on, man.
- Fuck this.
I'm just... I'm too thirsty to do this.
And the fucking bitter irony is I'm not gonna
have my thirst quenched until I finish this.
- God damn it, I hate it.
- Danny, no.
Don't walk away.
Danny, don't walk away from me!
It's too late, Seth.
I've already walked away too much.
No, you haven't.
You could still come back
and just fucking turn around
and come back and help me.
Danny?
Daniel?
Need a hand?
Yeah, dude.
Your shift just ended, man.
You don't have to help me
if you don't want to.
It's fine, I get it.
The fuck else am I doing?
I appreciate it, man. Thank you.
- Done and done.
- That's cool.
I don't know why I'm thinking of this,
but remember that time
that I got you a fucking
Taco Bell gift certificate
for, like, 20 bucks, and I bet you
that you couldn't eat all of that in one sitting.
I do remember that.
I remember thinking,
"How much food could 20 dollars
possibly buy you at Taco Bell?"
And the answer is infinite.
And we went to see fucking Gladiator.
- Yeah.
- And you sharted midway through the movie.
- I did.
- Due to the tigers' appearance.
- I got scared of the tigers.
- Yeah.
Literally, when the second
tiger came out, I went...
...and then I shat.
I shat in the theater.
- Jesus.
- Oh, fuck.
You guys Okay?
- I broke my ass in half.
- Here.
Shit, they got through!
- You guys fucking did it.
- Oh, my God.
- Fuck. Did that hurt?
- Yes, it fucking hurt.
I loosened this up for you,
I'll have you know.
Okay, just shut up.
It's fucking dark down here.
Hold on, hold on.
Nice.
- Okay, good. Thank you.
- What is that?
That's Terrence Peterson.
My monkey flashlight keychain.
Monkey flashlight keychain?
- What's his name?
- Terrence Peterson.
- You see it, Seth?
- No. Where...
Are you sure it's even down here?
Terry Pete.
Not sure.
Is there, is there
any weird shit down here?
Nah, it's where I keep
all my stuff from my old movies.
Costumes, props.
- What?
-ls someone down there?
It's your fucking stupid
cutout from Spider-Man 3.
Jesus Christ.
No shit!
- There it is!
- Yes! Yeah!
- What, did you find it?
- Yeah!
Water.
That is so fucking good.
The two heroes over here,
breaking through the floor.
We did break through the floor.
Any of you guys would
have done the same thing.
Oh, man. That fucking hurt.
Yeah, I'm surprised you didn't shart again.
I think I did.
Hey, what year is this? 19...
That's a good...
That's a good year.
Hey, hey. Yo, yo, yo!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
Fuck, man.
I'm just pouring myself
another glass of water
to wash down that dry-ass
Cinnamon Toast Crunch.
That's very nice, but you can't just
pour yourself another glass of water, man!
Will you cut it out?
- Yeah.
- We agreed to one glass at dinner,
we voted on it, man.
Well, man, I'm just getting sick and tired
of all these fucking rules, man.
You don't see me
putting rules on you guys.
You cannot have another glass of water.
Jay weighs 150 pounds less than me.
Why the fuck is it fair
that him and I should drink
the same amount of water?
We should be dividing our rations
based on our proportionate size.
I don't want to come off
as a diva here or anything.
It's just that I think everyone
should split everything equally.
"I just think that everybody
should have the fucking same.
"I have a goddamn earring."
Shut the fuck up, Jonah!
You know what, Danny? If you weren'tjizzing
all the time, maybe you'd be more hydrated.
You're making me into a joke
right now, Franco,
and you are not gonna like
the fucking punch line.
No more jerking off! No more water!
Just sit the fuck down!
Okay, I'm done.
We're not gonna have any more water.
- Good.
- All right.
Hey!
Someone help me!
Fucking grab it!
What are you doing?
You guys made this happen!
You guys forced my fucking hand
by ganging up on me.
God damn it, I'm gonna fucking
kill this motherfucker!
That's what I thought. Nerd.
All right, guys,
let's get rid of him.
What? What do you mean?
Like, kick him out of the house?
His fucking reckless behavior is
dragging us all down.
I mean, he wasted our water twice.
Two times. Two times.
Dan is under a lot of pressure. Okay?
And he's not handling it
as good as the rest of us are.
Look at him.
He's wearing my fucking tuxedo.
He's been eating nonstop.
The fucker's gained weight since he got here.
The fucker's got to go.
Go.
This is how you all feel?
We talked about it.
You guys are gonna
vote me off the island?
I mean, I made you guys breakfast.
Shit, man, you wasted half
of our food when you did that.
Just thought I was doing
something nice for you guys.
Just to apologize
for my behavior at the party.
Party I wasn't even invited to.
I'm not an idiot.
I know why you guys don't fucking call me
or hang outwith me anymore.
It's because I party so fucking hard.
Always have. Ever since I was a baby.
I wouldn't just suck on my mama's titties.
I would fucking bang 'em and motorboat 'em.
Everything I've been doing
has just been a cry for help.
When I came on your magazine, James,
it was a cum for help.
I've just been crying and c:omin'
and crying and c:omin',
tears from the tip of my penis, dudes.
I'm sorry, all right?
You can cum wherever you want.
I don't even care about coming anymore.
Right now, I'm just kind of into going.
- Danny.
- Hey.
- Come on, man.
I fucked up.
I'm sorry, man.
Come on, look,
- I was wrong.
- I feel like shit, man.
I didn't want it to happen like this.
- Let's just discuss it some more, okay?
- Yeah. Let's just talk, dude.
We're giving you an option.
It's a choice, man.
There's nothing to figure out, all right?
You guys have said enough,
and there's no going back anymore.
I don't know if there maybe is, like,
something you guys could give me
so I could at least have some sort of
protection while I'm out there.
Danny, you don't have to do this.
- Yeah, man.
- All right,
if you're really leaving
then you should take this.
Really?
You don't know what's out there.
Thank you, James.
It means a lot to you,
and I appreciate that you'd give this to me,
you stupid, stupid motherfucker!
Fucking psychopath.
It's a prop gun!
What, do you think
I'd put real bullets in here?
You were gonna send me out there
with a fucking gun
-filled with blanks?
- Fuck you!
Don't turn this around on us.
You just tried to shoot us,
you fucking dickhead!
Fucking murdering motherfucker!
Whatever.
Fucking civilization is broken down.
There's no more reason
for this false bullshit.
You guys act like you're
so fucking high and mighty,
like you've never made
a goddamn mistake before.
Franco, you're just
a pretentious fucking nerd.
Fuck you.
And, Jonah,
you fucking cunt.
Craig, you didn't have my back, back there.
- You fuckin' disappoint me.
- Bro.
And, Seth, you duplicitous taint.
- What?
- Then of course, there's Jay,
the self-righteous,
cock-sucking, two-faced backstabber.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I overheard your little
conversation with Craig, all right?
The only reason
why you care about any of us is
because you think
that's what God wants you to do.
You don't give a shit about us.
No, no, no, no, that's fucking
twisting that shit... You're fucking lying.
Am I twisting this?
I believe you were in Los Angeles
two months ago, at the Four Seasons.
I saw you there, and you specifically
asked me not to tell Seth,
so that you could maintain the illusion
that you always stay with Seth
when you're in Los Angeles.
Jay.
- Fuck, man.
-It's not...
Textbook twattage.
And just for the record, you guys,
I'm choosing to leave,
you're not kicking me out.
You guys had already said that
I could come back in
and I'm the one who said
that I'm not coming back in.
Don't be cocky.
Get the fuck out of here.
Is that true?
Yes.
J3Y--'
I know this is probably my fault
because I put you on a pedestal,
but you should not be
dishonest with your friends.
But you really let me down.
- Hey! Whoa!
- Jay, damn, man.
- Fucken
- What the hell?
It's all fucked, isn't it?
- Jonah, you okay?
- Yeah.
Bleeding?
Yeah.
His insides hurt worse than my outsides.
Dear God,
I'd like to pray
to You for a second.
It's me, Jonah Hill.
From Moneyball.
I hate Jay so fucking much.
I think he might be the worst person
You ever created.
I don't want to judge You, but...
What's up? What were You thinking that day?
I love Seth, I love being his friend,
he's an awesome guy,
but it's like Jay is the last connection
to his shitty, weird Canadian life.
Just do me one favor, God.
Just kill Jay.
That'd be so tight.
Stop, man.
Seriously, Craig, stop.
Your nails are sharp.
This is no dream!
This is really happening!
No!
Something not that chill happened last night.
Yo, so, I just drank
my own pee for the first time.
And it ain't bad.
I never thought to do it.
I always thought, you know,
pee stink, whatever, but...
I think we all remember how this works.
Whoever gets the burnt match
has to go to one of Franco's
neighbors' houses,
get us some food and some water.
No-ho-ho. No, I'm not going first.
- I'll go first.
- Thank you.
Very mature of you. Thank you.
Yes!
Sorry.
Good job.
You okay, Jonah?
What's that?
You Okay?
Yeah. Just bad sleep. Crazy dream.
Here, Jonah.
Jonah.
- Okay.
- Shit.
Craigers, you feeling lucky?
Will history repeat itself?
Thank you.
You got this, dawg.
Seth! No! Not you!
I'm not going.
- What?
- I'm not going.
I'm bowing out.
I'm declining to go.
- What?
- Let me break it down for you.
I'm not fucking going.
You are definitely going.
Tell him he's fucking going.
Tell you what, why don't you
fucking go, Mr. Self-Righteous?
You're constantly saying what assholes
we are, how good you are.
You go get us some fuckin' water.
I will go.
Because I have
-something called honor.
- Fuck, fuck, fuck.
That's good. Yeah, you're very honorable.
I'll go with you, Jay.
Really?
Is it because of our pact upstairs?
Nah, 'cause you got them skinny-ass arms.
You couldn't carry enough to feed a hamster.
It's working.
Let's get that money.
Let's do it.
Yo. Out and to the left.
Bye.
Oh, my God.
What?
That's so sad.
Innocencelost
What is that?
Fire.
There's, like, fire everywhere.
Damn it!
Hey, hey!
Fuck, yeah. Let's go, let's go, let's go.
- Hello?
- Shut the fuck up!
- What?
- You yelling that shit for?
- We got to find out...
- Don't yell no more, man.
Crack you in the
head with this frying pan.
Okay. So we should probably split up,
cover more ground.
What you think this is, Scooby
-Doo?
We're gonna go in there,
we're gonna find the kitchen,
and get as much
shit as we can, together!
Then we're getting the fuck out of here.
- All right, all right.
- All right?
Hey.
What are you doing?
That should be me out there.
I totally fucked those guys.
Fuck was that?
- Oh, fuck!
- Is he okay?
Dude!Jonah!
What the fuck?
What do we do?
- Do you know first aid or anything?
- No.
- Jonah!
- I suck at first aid.
- Are you okay? Shit!
- Jonah?
Oh, no. Low blood sugar. LBS.
- LBS!
- He's having an LBS episode!
- I'll get the Milky Way!
- You get the Milky Way!
Jay.
Jonah, stay with me! Stay with me.
I got it, I got it, I got it, got it,
open his mouth.
- It's your friend, Seth.
- Open his mouth.
Open his mouth. Open his mouth.
I'll get this in there.
- Okay, okay.
- Shove it right in there.
Jonah. Milky Way, Jonah.
- You love the Milky Way.
- Yummy, yum.
It's not fucking working, man!
- What the fuck!
- How do we get it in there?
Chew it up, chew it up and spit
in his mouth like a baby bird.
- You just swallowed it, man.
-It's so good.
Give me a bite.
The second it hits your mouth is,
like, amazing.
- Okay.
- Open it.
What the fuck was that?
- That's Hebrew.
- That's not Hebrew.
It's fuckin' Latin or something like that.
I went to Hebrew school for six years.
That's not Hebrew.
You will drown in a river of blood.
The End of Days is here.
You will quiver
in the shadow of Kingdom Come.
Judgment Day is upon you.
The Apocalypse is nigh!
Hey, I think that's all it could fit.
Man, let's take this back to Franco's,
get the fuck out of here.
What are we going back for?
What are you talking about?
In theory, we could just fuckin' stay here.
And here, you don't have to sleep
in a friggin' tent under a dick.
- I like my dick tent.
- I'm just saying,
we could build a life here together, Craig.
I'd be really good to you.
All I know is I'm scared as hell,
and I just want to get back to our friends.
Yeah, but they're not my friends.
Seth is your friend.
We've been growing apart for years.
That's why I didn't stay
with him last time I was here.
And I stayed with him
this time to try and salvage it,
but clearly that didn't work out.
Jay, like it or not,
those assholes are all we got.
- Did you hear that?
- Yeah, that was a creak.
What is that?
What is that? Is that bile?
I don't know. It's cold.
Sniff it.
No. You sniff it.
- What?
- It smells like puke.
Don't get it on me!
- It's in my eyes!
- Dude!
-It's in my mouth!
- He's gone!
- Where is he?
- He's fucking gone!
Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit!
Please, God! Jesus, Jesus!
Fuck.
- Jonah!
Jonah, stop this!
- Please!
- Jonah, where the fuck are you?
Why did you vomit on us!
Bad Jonah! Stop!
Stop eating him!
Watch out! He's super strong!
Shit!
What is happen...
Oh, no!
I'm gonna tittie-fuck you, Seth.
Don't tittie-fuck me!
What are they, big B's or small C's?
I'm gonna push your titties together.
Push 'em together!
I'll get you something to help!
- I'll pass you something!
- Okay, pass it to me.
Fuck! Shit!
Seth!
We're getting crazy!
Come on! Come on!
Jesus, open, God damn you, open!
No,no,no,no.
Jesus“.
Oh, fuck.
- We gotta hide. We gotta hide.
- I know!
- He's coming! He's coming!
- I know he's coming!
I don't know what the fuck to do!
I don't know...
Where are you going?
Shit.
- Please go away.
- He's sniffing.
I'm so scared, James.
Be quiet.
- You're breathing really loud.
- Am I?
- Don't breathe through your mouth.
- Okay.
- Now you're doing loud nose breathing.
- Am I?
I don't know where else to breathe from.
- Is that...
- Seth.
Oh, shit. Don't move.
Shit, he's coming right this way. Oh, shit.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Get out of my way! Move! Move!
Fuck!
You Okay?
Come on!
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
What the fuck!
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
There's a fuckin' demon chasing us!
- A demon?
- Demon?
- What the fuck happened to you guys?
- That!
- It's Jonah!
- He's possessed!
He's crazy!
Oh, fuck! You brained him.
Is that... I was
supposed to do that, right?
Yeah.
Motherfucker.
- Fasten!
- Hurry!
- Fasten, God damn you, bastard!
- He's gonna be fuckin'
bad news when he wakes up!
He's fuckin' strong.
- My side's good.
- Oh, shit!
All right, I'll fuckin' hit him.
- Fuck! Come on, come on!
- Okay!
This shit's cray cray, guys.
I mean, it's, like, the real, like Apocalypse.
It's, like, the Book of Revelations,
like that means there's a God.
Right?
I haven't led my life as though there's a God
this whole time.
Who fuckin' saw that coming?
That there's actually a God?
I'd say 95% of the planet.
Jesus fucking Christ, man.
You might want to stay away
from saying that.
"Jesus fucking Christ"? Why?
- Why can't I say that?
- One of the Ten Commandments.
"Thou shall not take
the name of the Lord thy God in vain."
Jesus isn't the name of the Lord.
God is name of the Lord.
Jesus, God, it's all the same.
-It's the Trinity.
- Father, Son, Holy Ghost.
It's like Neapolitan ice cream.
I don't even know what
the fucking Commandments are.
Guys, I think this is sort of bullshit,
because we're all good people.
I can look at each one of you in the eye,
I know you're good.
- I'm good.
- We're four actors.
We bring joy to people's lives.
Yeah, but we don't do it for free.
We get paid handsomely,
much higher than the average profession.
It's not like it was just handed to any of us.
We've worked really hard to be here.
Yeah, pretend like it's hot when it's cold.
You sitting on the beach, it's freezing,
you in your drawers, talking about
something, everybody's surfing.
I think God might have just fucked up,
made a mistake,
and left us behind by accident.
I mean, He's got a
lot of shit on His plate.
It's not an oversight,
it's not a mistake, okay?
We got to face facts. We're here,
and there's a reason we're all here.
Why are you so sure?
I've done things, man. I...
I gouged a man's eyeballs out.
- What the...
- Fuck off.
- Craig.
- Well, I was a kid, man.
It was a fuckin' bar fight.
It was a bad foosball game.
He said I didn't call spinneys,
and I fuckin' called spinneys.
He got all in my face,
and I smashed a bottle across his face,
and the first eyeball was an accident,
but then I was, like, fuck it,
and I went for the second one.
It was fucked up.
But you know what?
That shit happens. I'm saying, that's...
I think that's why I'm here.
I got to admit something.
L.-
I fucked Lindsay Lohan.
She was fucked up. She was high.
It was at the Chateau Marmont,
and she kept banging on my door.
She kept calling me Jake Gyllenhaal.
That's fucked up.
Yeah, I said, "Call
me the Prince of Persia."
See, that's what I'm saying, man.
We've all done bad shit, you know?
We've done more bad shit
than good in our lives, and
it's time to pay the piper.
Whoa, shit!
Something's wrong.
God did this.
He gave us light, and
then He took it away.
You hear that?
It's the soundtrack of us going insane.
Damn, I wish there was something
we could do to help him.
I know what we can do.
The fuckin' stench.
Jonah Hill?
Jonah?
Jonah Hill.
Jonah Hill is no more.
Demon?
Yes?
Fuck. That's not good.
That's not good.
Jay, you fool.
I say unto thee,
the power of Christ compels you!
Does it? Does it compel me?
The power of Christ compels you!
- Does it, Jay?
- The power of Christ compels you!
Is the power of Christ compelling me?
Is that what's happening?
The power of Christ compels you!
Guess what? It's not that compelling.
Jay, you serious right now?
That's your fuckin' plan?
You're gonna repeat lines from The Exorcist?
I would assume
they did their fuckin' research.
- It's a movie!
-It's a manual.
It's a fuckin' training manual.
I say unto thee,
the power of Christ compels you!
The power of Christ compels you!
Geez, it hurts a little bit.
It's, like, this little sting.
The power of Christ compels you!
- Seriously, fuck off.
- The power of Christ compels you!
Jay?
- Holy shit!
- You're pissing him off, man.
- Just stop it!
- Jay!
- The power of Christ compels you!
- The power of...
- Get the fuck down!
- Don't fucking push me, asshole!
- Geez, man!
- Easy!
'Fuck You!
- You're a fucking asshole, you liar!
- Still?
- Yes. Still? Yes.
- Guys, guys, we got a possessed guy here!
Do we have to
argue about this right now?
- Let 'em fight.
- We got an exorcism to finish. Hello?
Do you want to know
why I didn't stay with you?
- Yeah.
- You fuckin' changed.
You're a fuckin' sell-out.
You did fuckin' sell out.
Everyone says.
At least I did change! You act like
you're fucking 18 years old still, Jay!
Grow up, Jay. That's
why he's yelling at you.
You've been holding me back
this whole time!
That means fuck you.
Come on, guys! Come on!
Fuck you, you piece of shit!
Everybody, out!
Craig, stop 'em!
- Get apart!
- Now it's on.
Yo! What the fuck is all this, Franco?
Looks like food.
How'd that get there?
What? You have more food?
You knew he had extra food?
Yeah, he gave me one cracker.
I would have sucked a
dick for half a cracker.
All right, well, maybe I didn't want you
to suck my dick, all right?
- Look...
- I didn't want to suck it!
- That's the point of what I said!
- It was my fucking food!
- Guys, guys, guys, fire!
-Boys, boys, boys...
- Shit!
- Jonah's on fire!
Put it out!
Use your mouth! Put it out!
Go, go, go, go, 90!
- Where is he? Where is he?
- Where is he?
Go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, 90!
Go, get outside!
- Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit!
- Go, go on!
Come on, hurry up, he's coming!
He's coming!
Watch out, watch out!
Oh, my fortress!
Boys, I just want to point out,
we're out in the open now.
- Oh, fuck.
- Shit, shit, shit.
- Oh, shit.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- My Prius.
- Yeah!
- Yes!
What is that?
No fucking way.
We're screwed!
We're totally screwed, guys.
I got this.
- What?
- I'll distract the thing.
I'll run over there screaming and shit,
and that should give you enough time
to get to the garage.
Well, yeah, but that thing can kill you.
Maybe I deserve it.
I've been shitty my whole life.
Being selfish, only doing shit for me.
Maybe it's only right that
the last thing I do
on this planet isn't for me.
It's for you guys.
Craig, you don't have to do that.
Thank you very much, Craig.
- I appreciate that.
- You spineless...
I love you guys.
You're my best friends.
You're a real mensch, Craig.
See you on the other side.
Hey, hey, asshole! Hey, come on!
Pickle dick, demonic-looking motherfucker.
Nobody's scared of you.
You ain't a raccoon!
Yeah, bring your ass, bitch!
Nobody's scared of you!
I'm Craig fucking Robinson!
Yeah.
- What's he gonna do?
- Craig.
I hope you like big dick, motherfucker,
'cause I'm about to fuck you raw!
For the last goddamn time!
Take your panties off!
Fuck,yeah!
It worked.
What's happening?
Craig! Craig!
Holy shit, do you guys
realize what this means?
That Craig was an angel this whole time?
- No, no, it means we can still be saved.
- No, no.
I don't fucking get it,
why does Craig get saved? I mean...
Craig sacrificed himself for us,
which means that there's still hope.
- That means we can be redeemed.
- Yeah.
It means that if we're
actually nice to each other,
we can get sucked up into Heaven, too.
That's the deal.
All right, I got
it, let's just head out
-to my place in Malibu.
- Yeah.
Just survive long enough
until we do enough good things
and they accumulate
or do enough sacrifices,
and we'll all go to Heaven together.
That's a great idea, James.
Seriously, really, really good idea.
Really, you're such a smart guy.
Thanks, Seth, you're such a nice guy.
You got a great smile.
- Thanks, man.
- And an awesome laugh.
- I've heard it's annoying.
- How about that Jay back there, man?
- Dude, Jay, you kidding me? Come on.
- Come on.
- One of a kind.
- Get out of here.
You got a cool body. You can walk around
with your shirt off anytime.
It's not working, this isn't working.
What, you thought we would be
Raptured already?
I thought it would happen already.
No, we've just been talking nice.
Talking nice doesn't get you into Heaven.
Doesn't hurt to smile...
What the fuck?
You guys Okay?
- Oh, shit.
- Christ.
- Franco!
- Come on!
Yo, cut his fucking head off!
What's going on?
No!
"StOpl
- No!
- Danny?
- What the fuck?
- You guys are still alive?
- Yeah.
Holy shit, I didn't expect that.
Fuck out here.
Get...
- Shit, I can't believe you guys are here.
- Oh, Jesus.
That's fucking crazy,
and your timing couldn't be more perfect.
It's been a long time
since any of us have eaten,
and you three gentlemen look delicious.
- What does that have to do with us?
- The fuck are you talking about?
I'm a cannibal, hombre.
We're gonna fucking eat your ass.
Fuck you, you can't eat us.
Fuck that, man.
I do whatever the fuck
I want, when I want.
I butt-fucked this dude.
See that?
I fucking slide right in that shit.
I do whatever I want.
This is my gimp.
Channing, introduce yourself.
Hey, what's up, guys?
Y'all cool?
That's Channing Tatum.
That's Channing Tatum, dude.
What the fuck?
Channing fucking Tatum.
I found him wandering on the freeway.
I collected him, made him my bitch.
Get off my dick.
I call him Channing Tate-yum.
- Hard-core, man.
- I got him trained good.
Watch, he does tricks.
Wait, shake hands.
- All right, Seth.
- Fucking roll over.
- I'm gonna create a diversion.
- Yeah.
- You and Jay make a run for it.
- What?
Danny's gonna eat you.
Listen, full-on sacrifice for you, dawg,
-like the ending to Pineapple 2.
- Yeah, lick that.
- That's Channing fucking Tatum, dawg.
- I love him.
That's fucking G.l. Joe, dude.
Fucking loves me.
Danny! We're friends!
You can't eat us!
I'd love to catch up,
but we're fucking starving, so let's eat!
FUCK you!
Run!
Eat this!
Shit, fuck! Get him!
- Who wants it, you piece of shit?
- Man, we should go back.
- We should go back and help him.
- We should go back.
Fucking Rapture.
- Holy shit!
- It worked!
What the fuck?
Go to hell, McBride!
FUCK you!
Suck my dick!
- Oh, shit.
- What happened?
What did I do? Take me back!
- What did I do?
- I'll tell you what happened, Franco.
You don't get to get sucked up into Heaven
'cause you were being petty. Tom Petty.
You may not have
invited me to your party,
-but you're the guest of honor at mine.
- What?
How fucking crazy is this?
Seth, Jay!
Oh, shit, they're running after us.
Oh, shit! Oh, shit! Oh, shit! Run.
Bring them to me!
- Fuck.
- Get 'em!
Got to get Rogen.
Over here.
- What? Over here, over here.
- Here. What?
Shit, shit.
They're around here somewhere.
They kept running, you fucking idiots.
Shit, are they still there?
- I think they're gone.
- Are they gone?
- Oh, my God.
- Why did Franco flip off Danny?
Why did he have to do that, man?
- He was in the clear.
- That is textbook.
Vanity or...
- Is it vanity?
- Vanity or envy.
Is it envy or wrath?
- It's any of them, man.
- You can't do that.
It's being a sore
winner, is what it is,
-more than anything.
- That's exactly what it is.
- You can't be a sore winner.
- No.
Well, this is another fine mess
we found ourselves in.
Fuck.
Listen, Jay...
Oh, shit.
Get out of here,
let's get out of here.
You've got to be fucking shitting me!
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, no.
- That thing's big.
- Holy shit.
It's so big.
Oh, man. Oh, Jesus.
- We're gonna die, man.
- Okay.
Okay, we're gonna die.
- Jesus!
- Oh, no!
- Shit.
- Listen to me, man.
I'm a fucking idiot.
I put myself up.
I'm self-righteous.
- I think I'm better than you.
- No, no.
I was resistant to change.
- No.
- I should have grown with you.
I should have changed with you.
We should have changed together.
I didn't like what I became
so I hated what you became.
It's fine, man. It's fine.
- I love you, Seth, fucking love you, buddy.
- I love you, man.
- I always loved you.
- Let's die together, man.
- Let's die together.
- I love you, Jay.
- Holy shit, Jay, all right!
- Yeah, we did it!
I'm not getting sucked up into Heaven!
What do you mean? Why not?
I don't know why not!
Take my hand!
Okay, take me with you, Jay!
I'll take you with me.
Yeah!
- Yeah!
-It's working!
Yeah!
Oh, no! He sees us!
He can't touch us!
We're in a force field!
Oh, shit! Shit!
It's not gonna take me with you!
We're going down!
Keep holding on
and you'll get pulled up, too!
It's not! No, I won't, man!
I don't deserve to.
Fuck.
I'm gonna let go, Jay.
You'll die!
I know, but you won't.
No!
I don't deserve to go
to Heaven, but you do.
You do, okay?
We're both gonna die
if I don't let go.
I'm not gonna hold you back anymore.
No!
Yeah!
Come, hold my hand, buddy!
Hold my hand!
- Yeah!
- You did it!
You did it!
Yeah!
We're flying!
- Look!
- What?
Wow.
Welcome to Heaven, motherfuckers.
Craig!
- Yay!
- Yeah !
- Craig.
- Oh, my...
- What?
- This is awesome.
- Are you an angel?
- Yes, sir.
- That's so cool, man.
- That is so cool.
Congratulations, dude.
Fellas.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Dude, you got one.
- What?
- That's so cool.
- Do I have one?
- I can't see it.
- Do I have...
- Wait.
- Let's touch 'em.
- Dude, this is so...
- Wow.
- What do we do now?
- Yeah.
Come this way.
Right? Do you love it?
Do you love it?
Whoa, they got weed in Heaven?
- What?
- You tell me.
What?
Holy shit! That's awesome!
Wow.
That's insane, man.
No,no,no,no,no,no.
That's Heaven.
Anything you could think of is yours.
Whoa!
Holy shit, this is awesome.
Segway!
I've always wanted to ride
one of these things.
Go ahead, Jay, make a wish.
Anything you could think of.
Anything?
What?
No fucking way.